

IEVGEN BOBROV

FOOTBALL COACH UEFA B • MSc EX-PRO FUTSAL PLAYER









ABOUT ME

A highly driven, passionate and forward thinking coach which uses different skills and tools to build confidence and empower players to realize their potential. Delivered positive improvements, visible results and sustainable success with every club and company worked with. Inspired and served as a role model to young players in achieving fitness and good health.



QUALIFICATION

- Master of Science (with distinction) Sport Performance Coaching, University of Stirling, Scotland, UK;
- UEFA B Coaching License No1257;
- UEFA C Coaching License No1700;
- NSCAA Diploma Course "Get a Head Safely in Soccer";
- NSCAA Level 1 Diploma;
- FA CPD Course: Behavioural Management;
- U.S. Soccer Federation F License.



WORK EXPERIENCE

2012 - 2014 • MFC DELIVERY

(Professional Futsal Club, Ukraine)

Assistant of the Head Coach

- shadowed MFC Delivery Head Coach on a daily basis;
- observed planning, preparation and structure of the training sessions, pre-game and post-game analysis in a professional futsal environment;
- analyzed tactical principles and methods of elite professional coaching on a consistent basis;
- assisted with the set-up and organization of MFC Delivery training

2014 - Apr.2020 FC SHENZHEN EASY STRIKERS

(Youth Football Club. China. Shenzhen)

U8, U10, U12 Teams Football Coach

- designed and conducted all training sessions including all tactical and technical aspects of the game;
- created the Elite Team Program for U8's;
- developed game strategies for competitions;
- organized registration and tryout sessions, provided individual and team evaluations;
- scouted players, identified and recruited players;
- formed relationships with other coaches and clubs;
- communicated with parents on a regular basis to provide a better understanding, expectation and transparency for the families of players.

Apr.2020 - present Present FC SHENZHEN GREENFIELD (Youth Football Club, China, Shenzhen)

U7 - U12 Teams Football Coach

- designed and conducted all training sessions including all tactical and technical aspects of the game;
- ensured every controllable factor was held to an elite standard on a daily basis: punctuality, appearance, organization, work ethic and attitude;
- developed game strategies for competitions;
- formed relationships with other coaches and clubs;
- encouraged students to participate in physical activity even outside of the class.

Jan. 2020 • FCLOCOMOTIVE

(Proffesional Football Club, Georgia, Tbilisi)

Internship Visit

- shadowed FC Locomotive Tbilisi Coaching Staff on a daily basis;
- observed planning, preparation and structure of the training sessions in a professional football environment;
- · learned FC Locomotive Tbilisi playing philosophies, teaching methods, environment, standards and the culture of the club;
- assisted with the set-up and organization of FC Locomotive Tbilisi training sessions.